在这段视频中 我想很快地介绍一下这门课程
(字幕整理：中国海洋大学 黄海广,haiguang2000@qq.com )
In this video, I want to just quickly step you
through the logistics of how to work on
做作业的流程 以及如何使用作业提交系统
homeworks in this class and how to use the
submission system which will let you verify
这个提交系统可以即时检验你的机器学习程序答案是否正确
right away that you got the right answer for
your machine learning program exercise.
这是我的 Octave 编程窗口 让我们先进入到我的桌面
Here's my Octave window and
let's first go to my desktop.
我在我的桌面上保存了我的第一个练习和一些文件
I saved the files for my first exercise,
some of the files on my desktop:
在 'ml-class-ex1' 目录中
in this directory, 'ml-class-ex1'.
我们提供了大量的文件 其中有一些需要由你自己来编辑
And we provide a number files
and ask you to edit some of them.
因此第一个文件应该符合编程练习中 pdf 文件的要求
So the first file should meet the details in
the pdf file for this programming exercise.
其中一个我们要求你编写的文件是 warmUpExercise.m 这个文件
But one of the files we ask you to edit is
this file called warmUpExercise.m, where the
这个文件只是为了确保你熟悉提交系统
exercise is really just to make sure that
you're familiar with the submission system.
所有你需要做的就是提交一个5×5的矩阵
And all you need to do is
return the 5x5 identity matrix.
因此这个练习的答案 我给你们写过 就是 A = eye(5)
So the solution to this exercise I just
showed you is to write A = eye(5).
这将修改该函数以产生5×5的单位矩阵
So that modifies this function to
generate the 5x5 identity matrix.
现在warmUpExercise() 这个方程就实现了返回5x5的单位矩阵
And this function warmUpExercise()
now returns the 5x5 identity matrix.
将它保存一下
And I'm just going to save it.
所以我已经完成了作业的第一部分 现在回到我的 Octave 窗口
So I've done the first part of this homework.
Going back to my Octave window,
现在来到我的目录 C:\Users\ang\Desktop\ml-class-ex1
let's now go to my directory,
'C:\Users\ang\Desktop\ml-class-ex1'.
如果我想确保我已经实现了程序 像这样输入'warmUpExercise()'
And if I want to make sure that I've implemented
this, type 'warmUpExercise()' like so.
好了它返回了我们用刚才写的代码创建的一个5x5的单位矩阵
And yup, it returns the 5x5 identity matrix
that we just wrote the code to create.
我现在可以按如下步骤提交代码 我要在这里目录下键入 submit()
And I can now submit the code as follows.
I'm going to type 'submit()' in this
我要提交第一部分 所以我选择输入'1'
directory and I'm ready to submit part 1
so I'm going to enter choice '1'.
这时它问我我的电子邮件地址 我们打开课程网站
So it asks me for my email address.
I'm going go to the course website.
这是一个内部测试网站 所以你的版本可能看起来有点不同
This is an internal testing site, so your version
of the website may look a little bit different.
这是我的电子邮件地址 和我的提交密码 我需要在这里输入
But that's my email address and this is my submission
password, and I'm just going to type them in here.
所以我的邮箱是 ang@cs.stanford.edu 我的提交密码就是 9yC75USsGf
So I have ang@cs.stanford.edu and
my submission password is 9yC75USsGf.
按下回车键 它连接到服务器 并将其提交
I'm going to hit enter; it connects to the server
and submits it, and right away
然后它就会立刻告诉你 恭喜您 已成功完成作业1第1部分
it tells you "Congratulations! You have
successfully completed Homework 1 Part 1".
这就确认了你已经做对了第一部分练习
And this gives you a verification
that you got this part right.
如果你提交的答案不正确 那么它会给你一条消息 说明
And if you don't submit the right answer,
then it will give you a message indicating
你没有完全答对
that you haven't quite gotten it right yet.
您还可以继续使用此提交密码 也可以生成新密码 都没有关系
And you can use this submission password and
you can generate new passwords; it doesn't matter.
但你也可以使用你的网站登录密码 但因为这个密码
But you can also use your regular website
login password, but because this password
会在显示器上直接显示 所以我们给你额外的提交密码
here is typed in clear text on your monitor,
we gave you this extra submission password
因为你可能不希望输入你登录网站的密码
in case you don't want to type in your
website's normal password onto a window
你的密码是否会显示出来 取决于你使用的操作系统
that, depending on your operating system,
may or may not appear as text when you type
你的密码是否会显示出来 取决于你使用的操作系统
it into the Octave submission script.
这就是提交作业的方法
So, that's how you submit the
homeworks after you've done it.
祝你好运 当你完成家庭作业的时候 我希望你都能答对
Good luck, and, when you get around to
homeworks, I hope you get all of them right.
最后 在下一个也就是最后一个 Octave 的视频教程中 我将介绍
And finally, in the next and final Octave
tutorial video, I want to tell you about
向量化(vectoriazation) 这种方式可以使你的 Octave 代码更有效率地运行
vectorization, which is a way to get your
Octave code to run much more efficiently.